https://byington.com/privacy-policy/

Byington Vineyard & WineryVISITBYINGTONLos Altos Tasting RoomBOOK AN EXPERIENCELive MusicABOUTABOUTGiving BackNewsletterMedia KitPrivacy PolicyWine ClubJoinMember LoginMember EventsShop WineVirtual EventsEventsCorporateWeddingsLive MusicShopWineeGift CardsDistributionContactEventsGeneral InquiriesCharity Auction ProgramByington Vineyard & WineryVISITBYINGTONLos Altos Tasting RoomBOOK AN EXPERIENCELive MusicABOUTABOUTGiving BackNewsletterMedia KitPrivacy PolicyWine ClubJoinMember LoginMember EventsShop WineVirtual EventsEventsCorporateWeddingsLive MusicShopWineeGift CardsDistributionContactEventsGeneral InquiriesCharity Auction ProgramPrivacy Policy for Los Altos Vineyards LLD dba Byington Vineyard & WineryThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.byington.com, www.byington.wine, www.losaltostastingroom.com, Byington Vineyard & Winery. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by these websites, our landing pages, and our Facebook ads.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. The only information we have access to is the information you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you – including any information forms you fill out on this website, our landing pages, or Facebook ads. We will never sell or rent this information to anyone.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new products or service or special offers. We also may contact you to disclose any changes to this privacy policy.Your Control Over InformationYou may, at any time, opt out of any future contacts from us. You are welcome to contact us via the email address and phone number posted on our website (and listed below) to 1) see what data we have about you, if any, 2) change or correct any data we have about you, 3) request that we delete any data we have about you, 4) express your concerns about our use of your data.SecurityWe take every precaution possible to protect your information. The data you submit via our website or our landing pages or our Facebook ads is protected both online and offline. Only employees of Byington Vineyard & Winery who need the information to perform a specific job (for example billing or customer service) are granted access to this information. The computers and servers where we store personal information are kept in a secure environment.RegistrationThere are certain “resources” contained within our website that require the user to voluntarily provide certain information (such as name, company, and email address) before you can download these resources to your personal computer. This information is used to contact you about the products and services of Byington Vineyard & Winery for which you expressed an interest. You are welcome, at your option, to provide other demographic information (such as age or gender) about yourself, but this is never required.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other sites that collect personal information.RedressIf, at any time and for any reason, you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us immediately via telephone at 408-354-1111 or info@byington.com.
